LabValuesQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "The normal range of albumin is ____-____ g/dL",
        "answer": "3.5-5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albumin is synthesized in the l____",
        "answer": "liver",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albumin maintains plasma o____ pressure, binds and transports h____, d____, f____ acids, i____",
        "answer": "osmotic, hormones, drugs, fatty, ions",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albumin has a serum half life of ____ days",
        "answer": "20",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hypoalbuminemia is not caused by",
		"choices": "chronic liver disease, malabsorption/malnutrition, severe burns/trauma, alcohol use/ascites (extra abdominal fluid), overeating",
        "answer": "overeating",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal range of prealbumin is ____ mg/dL",
        "answer": "16-40",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prealbumin is used to determine n____ status",
        "answer": "nutritional",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prealbumin has a shorter half life span of ____ days compared to albumin which has a half life of ____ days, s____ body pool, more s____ to protein nutrition, less affected by l____ disease, not involved in o____ ",
        "answer": "2, 20, smaller, sensitive, liver, osmoregulation",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "total protein is a____ + g____",
        "answer": "albumin, globulin",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "globulin is made o____ the liver",
        "answer": "outside",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The liver synthesizes six coagulation factors ____, ____, ____, ____, ____, ____",
        "answer": "I, II, V, VII, IX, X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vitamin K is a c____ for activation of clotting factors ____, ____, ____, ____",
		"answer": "cofactor, II, VII, IX, X",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is not a cause of elevated PT",
		"choices": "vitamin K deficiency, vitamin K malabsorption (tetracycline), vitamin K antagonist (warfarin), systemic lupus erythematosus, disseminated intravascular coagulation, substantial hepatic impairment, vitamin K excess",
        "answer": "vitamin K excess",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Prothrombin time has been replaced by i____ n____ r____",
        "answer": "international, normalized ratio",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "the INR attempts to standardize test used to monitor w____ therapy and measures how long it takes blood to form a c____",
        "answer": "warfarin, clot",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "to standardize thromboplastin, the manufacturer inclcudes the i____ s____ i____",
        "answer": "international sensitivity index",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "INR= ____/____",
        "answer": "PT patient, PT reference plasma",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Aminotransferase is released into the serum where there is c____ damage",
        "answer": "cell",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "AST and ALT are located in h____, c____ muscle, k____, b____",
        "answer": "hepatocytes, cardiac muscle, kidneys, brain",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "AST/ALT ratio is useful in diagnosing a____ liver disease where AST is ____X ALT",
        "answer": "alcohol, 2",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lactate dehydrogenase is found in h____, l____ s____ muscle, b____, l____, k____, R____",
        "answer": "heart, liver, skeletal, brain, lung, kidneys, RBC",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lactate dehydrogenase is elevated in M____, m____, b____, m____, a____",
        "answer": "MI, myocarditis, burns, malignancy, anemias",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cholestasis is f____ to move bile from liver to d____",
        "answer": "failure, duodenum",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Alkaline phosphatase (ALP) ____X normal suggest a cholestatic disorder",
        "answer": "4",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "lactate dehydrogenase is not specific to liver function",
		"choices": "true, false",
        "answer": "true",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "5' nucleotidase is e____ in h____ tissue",
		"answer": "elevated, hepatic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "E____ ALP with n____ GGTP or GGT points to a n____ etiology ",
        "answer": "elevated, normal, nonhepatic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "GGT/ALP > ____ is highly indicative of a____ abuse",
        "answer": "2.5, alcohol",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bilirubin is the b____ of h____",
        "answer": "breakdown, hemoglobin",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "U____ bilirubin is water i____, and c____ bilirubin is water s____",
        "answer": "unconjugated, insoluble, conjugated, soluble",
        "type": "fill"
	},
    {
        "question": "Unconjugated bilirubin is known as i____ bilirubin and is bound to a____, when elevated leads to h____ disease",
        "answer": "indirect, albumin, hepatocellular",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Conjugated bilirubin is known as d____ bilirubin and is r____ in feces, and removed by kidneys when elevated and leads to d____ urine color",
        "answer": "direct, removed, dark",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The range for total bilirubin is ____-____ mg/dL",
        "answer": "0.3-1",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "ONLY t____ and d____ bilirubin can be measured",
        "answer": "total, indirect",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bilirubin is increased in h____ disease, h____ (jaundice), obstruction to bile flow c____",
        "answer": "hepatocellular, hyperbilirubinemia, cholelithiasis",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ammonia is made in the l____ intestine",
        "answer": "large",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Accumulation of ammonia leads to altered mental status called h____ e____",
        "answer": "hepatic encephalopathy",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "To determine the type of ACS, you should look at c____ presentation of the patient, e____, c____ markers",
        "answer": "clinical, electrocardiography, cardiac",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The three cardiac markers are Tn____, Tn____, Tn____",
        "answer": "T, I, C",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tn____ is presen in both c____ and s____ muscle",
        "answer": "cardiac, skeletal",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal range of troponin cardiac marker is ____-____ng/mL",
		"answer": "0-0.5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Echocardiography uses s____ waves to create a m____ image of the heart",
        "answer": "sound, moving",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal range of TSH is ____-____ mU/L",
        "answer": "0.5-5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "T4 is called t____ and T3 is called t____",
        "answer": "thyroxine, triiodothyronine",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "T4 and T3 circulate in human serum in two forms b____ and u____",
        "answer": "bound, unbound",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for sodium is ____-____ mEq/L",
        "answer": "135-145",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value of potassium is ____-____ mEq/L",
        "answer": "3.5-5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for chloride is ____-____ mEq/L",
        "answer": "96-106",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for bicarbonate is ____-____mEq/L",
        "answer": "23-28",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for BUN is ____-____mg/dL",
        "answer": "10-20",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for SCr is ____-____mg/dL",
        "answer": "0.6-1.2",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal value for glucose is ____-____mg/dL",
        "answer": "70-110",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "T____ has a higher resolution than T____",
        "answer": "TEE, TTE",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "TEE is used to detect v____ v____ in endocarditis and to detect a____ thrombi",
        "answer": "valve vegetation, atrial",
        "type": "fill"
    }
]